Guide to the Irish Echo Photographs AIA.045
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series II: Ireland, 1959-2004; 7.44 Linear Feet in 2 record cartons, 2 card boxes, 2 oversized flat boxes, and 3 manuscript boxes
  - Subseries II.D: Sports, 1975-1996
    - Durand, Derry, undated (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - GAA - Dublin Mealth Irelnd, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Gaelic Games, 1992 (Oversize 22, Folder 15, Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Gaelic Sports, circa 1975-1977, circa 1980s, 1992-1993, undated (Box 5, Folder 54-55, Oversize 22, Folder 16, Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Gaelic Sports - GAA Final Football, Cork & Derry, 1993 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - General Sports, circa 1970s-1980s, 1992-1997, undated (Oversize 22, Folder 17, Box 5, Folder 56, Box 23, Folder 12, Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Hurler of the Year, undated (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Lakes, Sean, undated (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - McGuigan, Barry, 1992, undated (Box 5, Folder 57)
    - Moley, Kevin (E.T.), undated (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - Moloney, Monty, undated (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - Morris, Michael "Mouse", 2010 (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - Newspaper Illustrations, 1988, undated (Box 5, Folder 58)
    - Nolan, Keith, undated (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - O'Donnell, Brendan, undated (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - O'Grady, Edward O., 2006 (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - Soccer - World Cup, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 22)
    - Sports Gaelic - GAA Ireland, Patrick "Punter" Culleton, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 24)
    - Sports Ireland Gaelic - Vinnie Halton, Donegal Senior Football Title, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Sports - Non Gaelic in Ireland, 1992 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Sports: Non-Gaelic in Ireland, Horse Racing, 1993 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Sullivan in Training, undated (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Subseries II.E: Subjects, 1919, 1969-2002
    This subseries contains a variety of photographs capturing moments in Irish life and culture. Major subjects include Irish architecture, Belfast's murals, general news in the country, and documentation of The Troubles.
    - Abbey Theatre, 1996, undated (Box 5, Folder 59)
    - Aer Lingus Workers Demonstrate Outside the Dail, 1983 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Art, 1988, 1990, 1996-1997, 2000, 2004, undated (Box 5, Folder 60, Box 20, Folder 4, Box 31)
    - Asgard, undated (Box 5, Folder 61)
    - Birmingham Six, 1990-1991, circa 1995, undated (Box 5, Folder 62)
    - Bishop in Galway Scandal - Annie Murphy & Gay Byrne on the Late Late Show, 1993 (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Bloomsday, 1982, 1988, 1994, 1996, undated (Box 5, Folder 63)
    - Charity, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 65, Folder 64)
    - Clergy, 1985, 1990, 1995, 1997, undated (Box 5, Folder 65, Folder 66)
    - Comhaltas Ceoltoiri Eireann Tour, circa 1977, 1987-1989, 2000, undated (Box 5, Folder 66)
    - Daffodil Day, undated (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Dail, 1919 (Box 5, Folder 67)
    - Dublin, undated (Box 5, Folder 68)
    - Dublin Historical Architecture, undated (Box 5, Folder 69)
    - Dublin - John McGarrick, 1994 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Dublin - May Day Parade/Carnival, undated (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - Education, undated (Box 5, Folder 70)
    - Education - School Band, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 16)
    - Events, 1992, 1995, undated (Box 5, Folder 71)
    - Fire Brigade (Dublin), undated (Box 25, Folder 23)
    - General, 1979, 1989-1999, undated (Oversize 21, Folder 12, Box 5, Folder 72)
    - Goal, 1989, 1992, 1995, undated (Box 5, Folder 73)
    - Guiness Fleadh, undated (Box 25, Folder 24)
    - Ireland - Trinity Ball (Student Life, Trinity College), undated (Box 25, Folder 25)
    - Irish Dolls, undated (Box 25, Folder 26)
    - Joyce, James, undated (Box 5, Folder 74)
    - Lourdes Pilgrim Assisted at Dublin Airport, 1993 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Minister of Defense David Andrews Reviews Troops for Somalia, 1993 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Miss Macra Festival, undated (Box 25, Folder 27)
    - Museums, undated (Box 5, Folder 75)
    - Negotiating Teams from Labour & Fianna Fail, 1992 (Box 32, Folder 46)
    - News, circa 1970, 1984, 1988-1989, 2002, undated (Box 5, Folder 76-77)
    - News Ireland - Dublin Mother Shopping for Children's Clothes, 1993 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - News Ireland - Irish Passport, undated (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - News Ireland - Irish Sailors and Gardai in a Sea Rider, 1993 (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Northern Ireland: General, 1969, 1972, 1979-1987, 1993-1996, 2002, 2004, undated (Box 16, Folder 32, Box 5, Folder 78)
    - Northern Ireland: Belfast Wall Murals, circa 1995 (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - Northern Ireland: IRA Target, undated (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Personalities, 1977, 1981, 1987, 1990, undated (Box 5, Folder 79)
    - St. Patrick's Day Parade (Dublin, Ireland), 1995 (Box 5, Folder 80)
    - Students, undated (Box 25, Folder 28)
    - Weddings, 1992-1993, 1999, undated (Box 5, Folder 81)
- Series III: United States, 1940-2004; 8.29 Linear Feet in 3 record cartons, 3 card boxes, 2 oversized flat boxes, and 1 manuscript box
  This series consists of photographic prints of various sizes. Photos in this series depict American businesses and politicians, as well as sports and athletes that were once the subject of the newspaper's reporting. Noteworthy subjects featured in this series include substantial documentation of Irish restaurants and pubs in America and an approximately 65-year photographic history of New York City's leading politicians. This series is divided into four subseries.
  - Subseries III.A: Business, 1977-2002
    This subseries contains photographs documenting successful Irish businesses in the United States. Popular subjects include Irish pubs, restaurants, and imports businesses.
    - Bank of Ireland, 1977, 1988, undated (Box 5, Folder 82)
    - Bank of Ireland - Group Picture Steps of St. Patrick's, undated (Box 32, Folder 21)
    - Bank of Ireland - Irish Crystal Display, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 18)
    - Banks, 1977, circa 1982, 1988-1989, undated (Box 16, Folder 34, Box 5, Folder 83)
    - Bronx Retail Restaurant Liquor Dealers Association Annual Outing, 1951 (Box Shared Tamiment 161, Folder 14)
    - Clodagh, undated (Box 23, Folder 24)
    - Emigrant Savings Bank, undated (Box 5, Folder 84)
    - Fitzpatrick's Hotel, 1992, 1994, undated (Box 5, Folder 85)
    - General Business, circa 1970s-1980, 1987-2002, undated (Box 5, Folder 86-87, Box 16, Folder 35)
    - Imports: General, undated (Box 16, Folder 36, Folder 37)
    - Imports: Beverages, 1990, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Imports: Crystal, 1987-1988, 1990, 1995, undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Imports: Stores, circa 1982-1989, 1994-2002, undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Imports: Pottery, 1989, 1995, 1999, undated (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Imports: Whiskey, 1987, 1994, undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Irish Business Organization (IBO) - Christmas Party, undated (Box 25, Folder 29)
    - Irish Traditional Bakery, undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Liffey Van Lines, circa 1995-1996, undated (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Metro-North Railroad, undated (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Pubs, undated (Box 25, Folder 30)
    - Restaurants and Pubs: Driving Hawk's, undated (Box 32, Folder 23)
    - Restaurants and Pubs: General, circa 1970-2001 undated (Box 17, Folder 1-9, Box 16, Folder 38-50, Box 6, Folder 8, Box 32, Folder 22)
    - Restaurants and Pubs: O'Reilly's Bar, undated (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - Restaurants and Pubs: Peter Timmins, undated (Box 32, Folder 17)
    - Restaurants and Pubs: Unidentified, undated (Box 17, Folder 10, Box 25, Folder 31)
    - Retail Business, circa 1992, 2001-2002, undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Steve Quinn Roger Smith Hotel, undated (Box 32, Folder 20)
    - UNID Resort, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - Subseries III.B: Politics, 1940-2004
    This subseries contains photographs of influential American politicians at every level of government, from City Councilmen to President. The politicians in these photos represent a range of ethnic backgrounds over approximately sixty years. The earliest photos in this subseries are of New York City politicians during the 1960s and 1970s, including images of former Mayor William O'Dwyer, a native of County Mayo, and of New York State Senator Robert F. Wagner. Also included in this subseries are topical headings, such as "State Politics" and "Women in Politics." An individual's folder, such as Joe Crowley, and a topical folder, like "State Politics," are not mutually exclusive.
    - A-F, circa 1950s-1970s, 1988-1989, 1993, undated (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - American Politics (General), circa 1970, 1976, 1985-1988, 1998, undated (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Anderson, Brian G., 1996, undated (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Biaggi, Mario, circa 1970, circa 1975, 1980-1988, undated (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Biden, Joseph, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Boyer, Sandy, undated (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Bradley, Brad (Senator), undated (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Brady, James, undated (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Brennan, Joseph, undated (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Brennan, Peter, undated (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Breslin, Jimmy, undated (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Brett, James, circa 1993 (Box 25, Folder 32)
    - Brown, Jerry, undated (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Buchanon, Pat, undated (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Bush, George, 1991, undated (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Bush, George H.W., undated (Box 25, Folder 33)
    - Carey, Helen, undated (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Carey, Hugh, circa 1970s, 1988-1989, 1999, undated (Box 6, Folder 25, Box 25, Folder 34)
    - Carter, Jimmy, undated (Box 33, Folder 30)
    - Clinton, Chelsea, undated (Box 25, Folder 35)
    - Clinton, Hillary, 1996, 2002, undated (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Clinton Irish Party at White House, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 24)
    - Clinton, William, 1991-1996, undated (Box 6, Folder 27, Box 25, Folder 36, Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Crowley, Joe, 1992, 1994, 2001, undated (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Crowley, Walter, circa 1985, undated (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Cuite, Thomas, 1977, undated (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Cuomo, Mario, circa 1977, 1988, 1993, undated (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Daley, Richard M. (Chicago Mayor), 1977, undated (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Daly, Richard, undated (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - D'Amato, Al (Senator), undated (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Dearie, John, 1977, 1984-1988, undated (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Dillon, Denis, 1985-1989, undated (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Dinkins, David, 1990, undated (Box 6, Folder 37, Box 25)
    - Dinkins, David and wife, undated (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - DioGuardi, Joseph, undated (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - Dodd, Chris, undated (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - Dole, Bob, undated (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - Donnelly, Brian, 1992, undated (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - Dornan, Bob, undated (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - Downey, Tom, undated (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - Drohan, William J., circa 1970s (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - Dukakis, Kitty, undated (Box 6, Folder 45)
    - Engel, Elliott, undated (Box 6, Folder 46)
    - Ferraro, Geraldine, undated (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - Ferrer, Fernando, undated (Box 6, Folder 48)
    - Fish, Hamilton, undated (Box 6, Folder 49)
    - Flynn, Raymond, 1988-1991, circa 1998, 2001, undated (Box 6, Folder 50)
    - Ford, Gerald, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 38)
    - G-L, 1965, 1975, 1977, circa 1982-1988, undated (Box 6, Folder 51)
    - Gilman, Benjamin A., 2002, undated (Box 6, Folder 52)
    - Giuliani, Rudolph, 1994, 1996-1998, undated (Box 6, Folder 53, Box 33, Folder 27)
    - Golden, Harrison, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 54)
    - Gore, Al, undated (Box 25, Folder 39)
    - Gulotta, Thomas, circa 1970s, 1985-1988, undated (Box 6, Folder 55)
    - Judges, circa 1970s, 1987-1996, 2001, undated (Box 6, Folder 58, Folder 56)
    - Kennedy, John F. (President), 1963, circa 1977, 1993, undated (Box 6, Folder 57, Box 32, Folder 44)
    - Kennedy, John F. (Jr.): Memorial, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Kennedy, Joseph P. (Jr.), 1988, undated (Box 6, Folder 58)
    - Kennedy, Ted, circa 1977, 1988, 1995, undated (Box 6, Folder 59)
    - King, Peter, 1982, circa 1984-1987, circa 1995, undated (Box 6, Folder 60)
    - Koch, Edward, 1985-1989, undated (Box 6, Folder 61, Box 25, Folder 40)
    - Kroll, Jonathan, undated (Box 25, Folder 41)
    - M-Q, 1975, 1988-1989, undated (Box 6, Folder 62)
    - Mackell, Thomas (Queens District Attorney), undated (Box 6, Folder 63)
    - Mackin, Sean, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 64)
    - Manton, Tom, 1986, 1990, undated (Box 6, Folder 65)
    - McGreevy Photos, 2004; TW_AIA_045_ER_3
    - McMillar, Bob, undated (Box 25, Folder 42)
    - Mitchell, George, 1996, undated (Box 6, Folder 66, Box 25, Folder 43)
    - Morrison, Bruce, 1994, undated (Box 6, Folder 67)
    - Moynihan, Daniel Patrick, undated (Box 6, Folder 68)
    - Murphy, John, undated (Box 25, Folder 44)
    - National Politics, circa 1960s-1990, 1999-2003, undated (Box 6, Folder 69-70)
    - New York City Government, circa 1970s, 1986-1996, 2002, undated (Box 6, Folder 71)
    - Nixon, Richard, undated (Box 6, Folder 72)
    - O'Dwyer, Bill (Mayor), 1940-1946, circa 1950, circa 1975, 1987, undated (Box 6, Folder 73)
    - O'Dwyer, Brian and Patricia King, undated (Box 25, Folder 45)
    - O'Dwyer, Paul, circa 1965, circa 1970, 1977, 1987-1996, undated (Box 6, Folder 74)
    - O'Neill, Thomas "Tip" (Congressman), circa 1984-1986, 1991, undated (Box 6, Folder 75)
    - Pataki, George, 1999, undated (Box 6, Folder 76)
    - Political Cartoons, 1981-1990, undated (Oversize 21, Folder 4, Box 6, Folder 77-78)
    - Quill, Mike, circa 1995-1996, undated (Box 6, Folder 79)
    - R-Z, circa 1970s, circa 1982, 1988-1994, undated (Box 6, Folder 80)
    - Reagan, Ronald, 1983-1987, undated (Box 6, Folder 81, Box 25, Folder 46)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson (Governor), circa 1960s-1970s, undated (Box 6, Folder 82)
    - Smith, Al, undated (Box 6, Folder 83)
    - Smith, Jean Kennedy, 1996, undated (Box 6, Folder 84)
    - State Politics, 1977-2002, undated (Box 6, Folder 85)
    - Torricelli, Robert G., undated (Box 25, Folder 47)
    - Wagner, Robert, circa 1960s, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 86)
    - Wilson, Malcolm, circa 1960s-1970s, undated (Box 6, Folder 87)
    - Women in Politics, 1985-1988, undated (Box 6, Folder 88)
  - Subseries III.C: Sports, 1970-2004
    This subseries contains photographs of various American sports, including baseball, American football, boxing, and darts.
    - American Football, circa 1970s, 1987-1989, 1996, undated (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Awards Ceremony, undated (Box 25, Folder 48)
    - Baseball, 1994, undated (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Baseball: Derek Jeter, undated (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Basketball, 1977, 1991, 1995, undated (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Basketball Players and Coaches (NBA), undated (Box 25, Folder 49)
    - Boxing, circa 1970s-1980s, 1992-2004, undated (Oversize 22, Folder 18, Box 7, Folder 4, Box 17, Folder 13-15, Box 34, Folder 14)
    - Darts, 1975, 1977, circa 1983, 1989, undated (Box 7, Folder 5, Box 25, Folder 50)
    - Field Sports, circa 1983, 1988, 1995, undated (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Horse Racing, circa 1970s, 1984-1995, undated (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - General Sports, 1963, 1977-1997, 2000, undated (Box 7, Folder 8, Box 29, Folder 8-11, Folder 13, Box 31, Box 34, Folder 2-4)
    - Golf, circa 1970s, 1987-1995, 2001, 2003, undated (Box 7, Folder 9, Box 25, Folder 51)
    - Hockey - Glen Hanlon, undated (Box 25, Folder 52)
    - Horse Racing - Breeder's Cup, undated (Box 25, Folder 53)
    - New York State Parks Games for the Physically Challenged, undated (Box 25, Folder 54)
    - Racing (Car, Boat), 1984, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Track and Running, circa 1970s, 1987-2001, undated (Box 7, Folder 10, Box 25, Folder 55)
    - Tug of War Trophy, undated (Box 25, Folder 56)
    - Unidentified Sports Awards, undated (Box 25, Folder 57)
  - Subseries III.D: Subjects, 1970-2003
    This subseries is comprised of two folders: Crime; and Labor and Unions.
    - 11th General Convention Building Service Employee's International Union, 1955 (Flat-file-folder 4, Tray 2)
    - Allied Irish Bank, undated (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Clydesdale Horses, undated (Box 25, Folder 61)
    - Concert at Tailors Hall, undated (Box 25, Folder 58)
    - Crime, 1995, 1999-2003, undated (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Events: New York City Kids' Fest, 2001 (Box 23, Folder 26)
    - Fishing, undated (Box 33, Folder 48)
    - Labor and Unions, circa 1970s-1982, 1989-2002, undated (Oversize 22, Folder 19, Box 7, Folder 12)
    - New York City, undated (Box 25, Folder 62)
    - Sotheby's Auction, 2001 (Box 25, Folder 59)
    - Statue of Liberty, undated (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Summer, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - Unidentified, undated (Box 23, Folder 25, Box 25, Folder 60)
- Series IV: Irish Echo Staff, 1971-2004; 2.65 Linear Feet in 1 record carton, 2 card boxes, and 1 manuscript box
  This series consists of photographic prints and multiple snapshot sequences of the Irish Echo staff at social functions. The contents of this series also include photographs of several members of the Grimes family, proprietors of the Irish Echo from 1955 to 2002. Additional subjects documented in this series include the newspaper's regular and contributing staff.
  - Connolly, Charles, undated (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Advertisements - Foods, undated (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Cull, Frank, undated (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Demographic Questionnaire (James Lyndon & Tara McAuliffe), undated (Box 32, Folder 32)
  - Grimes, Claire, 1997, undated (Box 17, Folder 16, Box 7, Folder 15, Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Grimes, Jinnifer and Claire, undated (Box 32, Folder 47)
  - Grimes, John, undated (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Grimes, Patrick H., undated (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Grimes, Patrick J., 1971, undated (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Holland, Jack, 2004, undated (Box 17, Folder 17, Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Irish Echo Soccer(?) Team, 1984 (Box 32, Folder 25)
  - Irish Echo Staff, 1991, 1993 (Box 32, Folder 43, Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Murphy, Eileen, undated (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - O'Hanlon, Ray, undated (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Staff: General, 1976-1977, 1987-1988, undated
    - Paper Materials (Box 7, Folder 20, Box 17, Folder 20-26, Box 23, Folder 27-29, Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Digital Materials, TW_AIA_045_ER_1
  - Staff: Irish Echo Event, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Staff: Photo Requests, undated (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Staff: Screening of Angela's Ashes, undated (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Staff: 70th Anniversary Party, undated (Box 17, Folder 28)
- Series V: Artists, circa 1938-2004; 6.33 Linear Feet in 4 record cartons, 2 card boxes, and 2 manuscript boxes
  Because of the fluidity and significance of cultural exchange between communities in Ireland and the United States, this series consists of photographic prints of both Irish and Irish American performers. Notable artists and bands featured in this series include playwright Seamus Heaney, authors Maeve Binchy and Frank McCourt, and musical groups such as The Chieftains and U2. Photographs documenting productions or adaptations of these artists and others are featured in Series VI. Film, Television, Theatre. This series is divided into two subseries.
  Contained in this series are two subseries, both of which are organized alphabetically according to artists' surnames or band name. Major artists and bands are listed individually. Lesser known artists and bands are featured in alphabetic sequences prefaced by "Individual Artists" or "General Bands," and then followed by a letter.
  - Subseries V.A: Individual Artists, 1925-2004
    This subseries primarily consists of photographs of Irish and Irish American actors, actresses, writers, musicians, and other performers. Some American artists with ties to the Irish American or Irish communities are also featured. The majority of these photographs are official headshots or taken on location.
    - Aengus, undated (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Aine, undated (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Allen, Woody, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Archway, Jim, undated (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Arthur, Davey, undated (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Ball, Lucille, undated (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Ball, Patrick, undated (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Barry, Sebastian, circa 1998 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Beckett, Samuel, 1959, 1985, undated (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Begley, Philomena, undated (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Begley, Seamus, undated (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Behan, Brendan, undated (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Bennett, Kathleen Mahony, undated (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Berenger, Tom, undated (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Bergin, Mary, 1988, undated (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - Big Tom, undated (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - Binchy, Maeve, 1991, undated (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - Black, Frances, 1995, 1997, undated (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - Black, Mary, 1997, undated (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - Bloom, Luka, undated (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - Bono, undated (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - Bowen, Elizabeth, undated (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - Bowyer, Brendan, 1996, undated (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - Boy George, undated (Box 7, Folder 43)
    - Bradshaw, Harry, undated (Box 7, Folder 44)
    - Brady, James, undated (Box 7, Folder 45)
    - Brady, Patricia, 1999, undated (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - Brady, Paul, 1993, 2002, undated (Box 7, Folder 47)
    - Branagh, Kenneth, 1994, undated (Box 7, Folder 48)
    - Brennan, Maire, undated (Box 7, Folder 49)
    - Breslin, Patricia, undated (Box 7, Folder 50)
    - Brighton, Pam, undated (Box 7, Folder 51)
    - Britton, Timothy, undated (Box 7, Folder 52)
    - Brocklebank, Jerry, undated (Box 7, Folder 53)
    - Brolly, Francie and Anne, 1987, undated (Box 7, Folder 54)
    - Brosnan, Pierce, undated (Box 7, Folder 55)
    - Brown, Christy, undated (Box 7, Folder 56)
    - Browne, Louis, undated (Box 7, Folder 57)
    - Browne, Vincent, undated (Box 7, Folder 58)
    - Burke, Joe "Banjo", 1980, 1987, undated (Box 7, Folder 59)
    - Burke, Kevin, 1991, 1993, 2002, undated (Box 7, Folder 60)
    - Burns, Batt, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 61)
    - Burns, Mary, undated (Box 7, Folder 62)
    - Busker, undated (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Butler, Jean, 1997, undated (Box 7, Folder 63, Box 32, Folder 37)
    - Byrne, Chris, undated (Box 7, Folder 64)
    - Byrne, Gabriel, 1993-1996, 2000-2001, undated (Box 7, Folder 65, Box 32, Folder 38)
    - Cagney, James, 1938, undated (Box 7, Folder 66)
    - Cahillane, Pat (Jr.), 1994 (Box 7, Folder 67)
    - Canny, Paddy, undated (Box 7, Folder 68)
    - Carr, Marina, undated (Box 7, Folder 69)
    - Carroll, Liz, undated (Box 7, Folder 70)
    - Carroll, Mike, undated (Box 7, Folder 71)
    - Carroll, Pat, undated (Box 7, Folder 72)
    - Carton, Mickey, 1988, circa 1991, undated (Box 7, Folder 73)
    - Casey, Karan, 1999, 2001, undated (Box 7, Folder 74)
    - Cash, Johnny, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 75)
    - Cashman, Nancy, undated (Box 7, Folder 76)
    - Cassidy, Patrick, undated (Box 7, Folder 77)
    - Cavanagh, Hugh J., circa 1925 (Box 7, Folder 78)
    - Clancy, John, undated (Box 7, Folder 79)
    - Clark, Mary Higgins, 1996, undated (Box 7, Folder 80)
    - Coates, Catherine, undated (Box 7, Folder 81)
    - Coen, Father Charlie, 2003, undated (Box 7, Folder 82)
    - Coen, Jack, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 83)
    - Colgan, Michael, undated (Box 7, Folder 84)
    - Collins, Barry, undated (Box 7, Folder 85)
    - Collins, Ray, 1986, undated (Box 7, Folder 86)
    - Conlon, James, undated (Box 7, Folder 87)
    - Connery, Sean, circa 1994 (Box 7, Folder 88)
    - Connolly, Andrew, undated (Box 7, Folder 89)
    - Connolly, Billy, undated (Box 7, Folder 90)
    - Connolly, Buddy, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 91)
    - Connolly, Mattie, 1989, undated (Box 7, Folder 92)
    - Connolly, Patricia, undated (Box 7, Folder 93)
    - Connolly, Seamus, 1989, 1998, undated (Box 7, Folder 94)
    - Considine, Bob, 1945, undated (Box 7, Folder 95)
    - Conway, Brian, 1997, 2002, undated (Box 7, Folder 96)
    - Cooney, Andy, undated (Box 7, Folder 97)
    - Corr, Finbarr, undated (Box 7, Folder 98)